

Aleksandrs Kornijenko

CURRICULUM VITAE

Profile

Experienced and hardworking logistics specialist, who has decided to take the challenge and start a career in the software testing field. Therefore, I've completed software testing courses and am ready to put new knowledge and skills into work!

Software testing for me is like solving a puzzle, trying to use all available methods, strategies, tools, and knowledge to find issues and fix them, providing the highest quality products to end customers.

My personal qualities, such as attention to detail, responsibility, reliability, together with many years of experience in creating and maintaining documentation, will lead to a successful start in the IT field.

Education & Courses

Selenium WebDriver with Java – Basic to Advanced + Frameworks, Udemy FEBRUARY 2022 - * IN PROGRESS

Software Testing, SIA Planet of Testing

NOVEMBER 2021 — JANUARY 2022

- Types of testing Test design techniques Test plans, test cases Basic SQL
- Quality reports Bug reports in Jira Basic VirtualBox Basic Postman

Java for beginners. From zero till Oracle certificate, Udemy

MAY 2021 — JUNE 2021

Construction engineer, Riga's Construction College

SEPTEMBER 2008 — SEPTEMBER 2012

Construction site specialist, Riga's Construction College

SEPTEMBER 2005 — SEPTEMBER 2008

Work experience

Head of Logistics Department, SIA ABX Terminal, Riga

JANUARY 2020 — MAY 2021

- Analysis and Planning Activity and efficiency reports Problem solving
- Organization and workflow control of department
- Optimization of the cost and efficiency of the enterprise operations

Head of Import Department, SIA ABX Terminal, Riga

SEPTEMBER 2019 — JANUARY 2020

- Communication with clients, suppliers, carriers Teamwork
- Formation of invoice, packing list, specification, contracts, customs documents
- External economic activity Logistics and business operations

Expedition agent, SIA ABX Terminal, Riga

FEBRUARY 2017 — SEPTEMBER 2019

- Coordination of logistic operations Status reports
- Daily work with 1C: ERP Formation of transport and customs documentation

Warehouse supervisor, SIA ABX Terminal, Riga

SEPTEMBER 2016 — FEBRUARY 2017

- Warehouse work organization - Customs cargo, resources, workflow reports

Warehouse keeper, SIA ABX Terminal, Riga

AUGUST 2012 — SEPTEMBER 2016

- Organization of cargo handling operations - Organization of worker shifts

Details

Emmas street 1, Riga, LV-1015, Latvia +37120352730 cornholio13@inbox.lv

DRIVER LICENSE

B Category driving license

DATE / BIRTH PLACE

21.04.1989

Riga

Sites

LinkedIn

Skills

Attention to details

Teamwork

Communication skills

Critical thinking

Languages

English

Latvian

Russian

Hobbies and interests

Software testing, basketball, guitar playing